大家好，美女们，欢迎收看这个视频。
Hello beautiful people and welcome to this video.
我们将执行最后一步，在虚拟机中设置您的a Buntu安装。
We're going to be doing the final step of setting up your a buntu installation inside the virtual machine.
虽然我们应该说，如果您确实在此过程中遇到任何错误，如您所知，它会显示虚拟的
Though we should say that if you do get any errors in this process like you know it says the virtual
机器崩溃只需在虚拟框中转到此处，单击设置系统，然后将此栏拖低一点
machine crashes just go over here in virtual box click on settings system and drag this bar a bit lower
向下进入果岭。
down into the green.
好的，只是为了给你的主机增加一点内存，以防万一。
Ok just that just to give your host computer or just a bit more memory in case it needs.
好的。
OK.
所以以防万一，但如果真的发生了，也不用担心。
So just in case that happens but don't worry if it does.
没什么不对劲的，把它合上就行了。
Nothing's gone wrong just close it.
把横杆缩小到果岭，然后再试一次。
Reduce that bar down to the green and then try again.
好的。
OK.
但是我们现在要做的是，我们将在虚拟框中打开，我们将单击
But we're going to do now is we're going to we're going to open in virtual box we're going to click
从我们的功能虚拟机开始。
start on our ability virtual machine.
这样做的目的是在我们的计算机中打开一台假想的计算机。
And while this is going to do is it's going to open up an imaginary computer inside our computer.
所以这真是太棒了。
So this is super awesome.
如果您想要安装一个Buntu，这就是您必须经历的实际过程
And this is the actual process that you would have to go through if you wanted to install a buntu for
REAL作为实际计算机上唯一的操作系统。
real as the only operating system on an actual computer.
所以现在开放的东西叫做虚拟机。
So what's opening up now is called a virtual machine.
它是计算机内部的一台虚构的计算机，它认为您正在上面安装操作系统
It's an imaginary computer inside a computer that thinks you're installing an operating system on it
因为我们是从那张直播CD启动的。
because we're booting from that live CD.
好的。
OK.
所以我们在上一段视频中下载所有假想的磁盘文件。
So all that imaginary disk file that we downloaded in the last video.
所以我们现在要做的就是在这个假想的
So what we're going to have to do now is we're just going to have to install a buntu on this imaginary
这是一个非常简单的过程，正如你所看到的。
computer and it's really easy process as you can see.
它现在已经打开了，它会给我们两个选项，它会说，试着安装两个。
It's opened up now and it's going to give us two options it's going to say try to install two.
我要先走一步。
I'm going to go ahead.
您要做的是单击安装，但请确保从侧面选择您想要的任何语言
What you do is click install to but make sure you pick whatever language you would like from the side
这里。
here.
我将它保留为英文，然后单击Install a Buntu。
I'm going to keep it in English and then click install a buntu.
好的。
OK.
因此，它将在这里为您提供一些额外的选择。
So with that it's going to give you some extra options here.
这两个箱子都拿去吧。
Take both of these boxes.
这将允许它在安装Kubuntu时更新、下载和一些更新。
This one is going to allow it to update download and some updates when installing Kubuntu.
这将安装第三方软件，如Wi-Fi硬件、MP3播放器和其他东西
And this is going to install third party software such as Wi-Fi hardware MP3 players and other stuff
只是为了让您了解您的体验更加完整，并让您的虚拟机变得您了解
just to make you know your your experience a bit more complete and make your virtual machine you know
只是比其他情况下多了几个功能。
just have a few more features than it would otherwise.
因此，请继续并选择这两个框，然后单击继续。
So go ahead and take both those boxes and then click continue.
然后它会给我们一些其他的选择，让我们在下一个屏幕上玩。
And then it's going to give us some other options to play with on the next screen.
这一点需要一点时间。
This bit's taking a little bit of time.
我们走吧。
There we go.
据说这台电脑目前没有检测到任何操作系统。
It's saying the computer currently has detected no operating systems.
你想做什么？你想做什么？
Would you what would you like to do.
嗯，只要点击一下就行了。
Well just click.
只需擦除磁盘并安装Buntu即可继续，然后单击Install Now。
Just have erase disk and install buntu to go ahead and click Install now.
系统会问您是否要写入更改，只需单击“继续”即可。
It's going to say do you want to write the changes just click continue.
那太好了。
That's perfectly fine.
现在它会问你，你现在在世界的什么地方。
And now it's going to ask you where in the world are you now.
这仅用于时区目的，您可以根据需要单击不同的区域
This is just for timezone purposes and you can click on different areas depending on what you might
如果你知道你在英国有美国，就穿你想穿的衣服，所以我要点击那里
wear where you might be if you know you've got the US over here in the UK so I'm going to click there
事实上，我想把伦敦作为我的时区。
and it's going to and actually I want to have London as my time zone.
这就是了，伦敦说，我们将单击继续，现在我们将要求您提供
So there we are it says London and we're going to click continue and now we're going to ask you for
您的键盘布局。
your keyboard layout.
我的是英语英国，所以我要，我要点击英语OK，这对我来说很好，但是
Mine's English UK so I'm going to I'm going to click English OK and that's going to be fine for me but
您可以，如果我只是返回，对不起，您可以通过单击检测键盘来测试您的键盘Leo
you can actually if I just go back sorry you can test your keyboard Leo by clicking detect keyboard
布局并键入这些键中的一个，如果我在那里按y，然后按另一个键，然后当前
layout and typing one of these keys if I press y in there and then another one and then is at present
不，不是。
no it's not.
它会帮我想出办法的。
It'll figure it out for me.
我应该使用哪个键盘。
Which keyboard I should be using.
然后它会帮我挑出来，挑出来还是不挑出来，但我也可以从列表中选择。
And then it will help me out pick it pick it out or not but I can just also select it from the list.
由你决定。
It's up to you.
英语对我来说很好。
English is fine for me.
你只要去选对你有利的就行了。
You just go ahead and pick whatever is good for you.
然后单击继续。
Then click continue.
然后它会询问您的用户名，所以我会把Ziyad作为我的用户名。
And then it's asking you for your username so I'm going to put Ziyad as my username.
它会要求我输入计算机名称，它可以自动生成，但我将调用我的
It's going to ask me for a computer name it can automatically generate that but I'm going to call my
虚拟盒子的VB选择一个用户名Ziyad，然后它会问我密码，我要
VB for virtual box picking a user name Ziyad and then it's going to ask me for passwords I'm going to
输入的密码是弱密码，不要对我评头论足。
enter a password is weak password don't judge me.
为一个很棒的密码干杯。
To a fantastic password.
现在我们已经输入了密码，它说需要密码才能登录并保持选中状态
So there we are we've entered that and it says require a password to log in and keep that checked and
这就是你真正需要做的一切。
that's all you really need to do.
但是一定要记住这个密码，因为它会在整个课程中非常有用。
But make sure you do remember this password because it will come very useful throughout the course.
如果您想使用您的虚拟机而不想被锁定，那么请记住这一点。
And if you want to use your virtual machine and not be locked out so do remember that one.
然后单击继续。
Then click continue.
现在它要做的就是将所有的Buntu安装到这个虚拟的
And now what it's going to do is it's going to go about installing all of a buntu onto this virtual
机器。
machine.
它很能说明问题，你是否知道你已经得到了一些信息，这些信息将以同样快的速度和充满新功能的方式点击。
And it's telling can you know you've got some information about to hit as fast and full of new features.
最新版本的Buntu使计算变得比以往任何时候都更容易。
The latest version of a buntu makes computing easier than ever.
这里只有几个很酷的新东西需要注意。
Here are just a few cool new things to look out for.
你可以点击这个箭头，它说找到更多的软件，告别了不得不搜索
And you can click on this arrow and it says find even more software say goodbye to having to search
可以访问软件商店的新软件的Web。
the web for new software with access to software store.
您可以轻松安装新应用程序。
You can install new apps with ease.
只需输入您要查找的内容，或在旁边浏览科学教育和游戏等类别
Just type in what you're looking for or explore categories such as science education and games all alongside
来自其他用户的有用评论。
helpful reviews from other users.
太棒了。
Awesome.
你可以把你的音乐带走。
You can take your music with you.
Buntu配备了令人惊叹的Rhythmbox音乐播放器，具有高级播放选项。
Buntu comes with the amazing Rhythmbox music player with advanced playback options.
制作完美的歌曲很简单，而且它与CD和便携式音乐播放器配合使用效果很好，所以您
It's simple to cue up the perfect songs and it works great with CDs and portable music player so you
无论你走到哪里，都能欣赏到你所有的音乐。
can enjoy all your music wherever you go.
太棒了，你可以不停地点击这些东西。
Wonderful and you can keep clicking through these things.
关于照片的东西。
The stuff about photos.
网页浏览，例如，它已经附带了Firefox，它还附带了自己的办公套件
Web browsing so it already comes with Firefox for example and it also comes with its own suite of office
软件所以基本上类似于Microsoft Word、Microsoft Excel、Powerpoint等软件。
software so basically similar software to Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Powerpoint and so on.
com免费下载。
Com for free.
它们还可以处理有用的Microsoft Office文件。
They could also work with Microsoft Office files that's useful.
如果您需要任何特定的辅助功能选项，您还可以选择他们所说的辅助功能选项。
You've got other things they said accessibility options if you need any particular accessibility options.
当您使用您的计算机时，它们也包括在内。
When you use your computer they also are included as well.
你可以拥有它们。
You can have them.
它告诉您一些来自Ubuntu团队的帮助和支持。
It tells you about some help and support from the Ubuntu team.
所以它所做的基本上就是在你的计算机上安装大量的软件
So what this is doing is it's basically just going to install loads of software on your computer it's
我也要做一个完整的捆绑安装，这可能需要一些时间，这取决于您知道，
going to do a full install of a bunch too and it might take a bit of time depending upon you know just
你的电脑安装东西真的有多快。
how quick your computer is installing stuff really.
所以我要做的是我要把视频放在这里然后我会回来的时候
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to keep the video here and then I'm going to come back when this
安装已经完成，并继续睡觉的方式。
installation has finished and to continue the rest of the way.
好的，我回来了，您可以看到安装现在已经完成。
OK and I'm back and you can see that the installation is now complete.
它显示您需要重新启动计算机才能使用新安装，因此我将单击
It says you need to restart the computer in order to use the new installation so I'm going to click
现在重新启动，应该会像这样关闭虚拟机，并显示要删除安装
restart now and that should shut down the virtual machine just like that and it says to remove the installation
5~6成熟。
medium.
请取出安装介质，然后按并执行此操作，我将按Enter键。
Please remove the installation medium then press and do so I'm going to press enter.
现在应该会再次启动Buntu虚拟机，但这一次不必
And that should now start booting up the buntu virtual machine again but this time without having to
请继续安装，我们等待它打开。
install it anymore us wait for this to open.
非常令人兴奋，我们开始吧。
Very exciting and there we go.
现在弹出来说，嘿，这是我的用户名，叫Ziyad。
It's now popped up and said hey here's my username which is Ziyad.
我可以单击我可以输入密码，然后单击Enter或Sign In，它将显示
I can click on that I can enter my password and click enter or click sign in and it's going to show
给我这个。
me this.
这个看起来相当棒的黑客玩意儿。
This rather awesome looking hacker stuff.
我们就到这了。
And there we are.
现在，我们已经在虚拟机上成功安装了Buntu。
We've now gone ahead and successfully installed a buntu on our virtual machines.
这不是很棒吗。
Isn't that awesome.
我们这里有什么，你可以知道，你可以看到，你已经安装了Firefox浏览器
What we've got here we can you know you can see you've got the Firefox browser installed you've got
Rhythmbox，就像一个音乐播放器。
Rhythmbox which is like a music player.
你有一些文件，就像你的文件导航器会在课程中经常用到的。
You've got files which is like your file Navigator will be using this quite a bit in the course.
您在这里安装了文件夹，您有软件中心，这将是您下载的一种方式
You've got folders installed here you've got software center which is going to be a way for you to download
Xserve软件我们不会在课程中直接使用它，但如果您想浏览，它就在那里
Xserve software we won't use this directly in the course but it's there in case you wanted to browse
一起来看看。
and have a look at.
你知道，你可以浏览一下旧的附加软件，你可以在这里看看，那里有这么多可供选择的东西
You know you can browse through the old Add-Ons you can have a look out here and there's so much to
做。
do.
你在这上面有不同的设置和东西，你可以看看你的设置
You've got up here you've got different settings and stuff you can take a look at your settings and
我真的想让你做的是，我想让你试一试这种东西，它很管用。
really what I want you to do is I want you to have a play around with this stuff it works.
这只是电脑族的事情。
It's just a computer guys kind of thing.
事情只是以一种不同的方式布局，但与什么相比，它不会太奇怪
Things are just laid out in a different way but it's it's not going to be too strange compared to what
你已经习惯了。
you're already used to.
事物可能有几个不同的名称。
Things might have a few different names.
有一件事是好的，那就是展示应用程序。
And one thing that's good is to show applications.
按下这里的按钮，当你点击它时，它会以一种相当棒的方式打开，向你展示一些
Button Down here which when you click that it will open up in a rather awesome way showing you some
安装的应用程序，您可以单击这些应用程序进行锁定，这样您就可以获得Thunderbird
applications that are installed that you can click on to have a lockout so you've got Thunderbird which
就像一个电子邮件客户端的视频，它向你显示视频，游戏，在这里，比如Margene。
is like an email client videos which shows you videos games and here such as Margene.
你有Liebreich Office，它就像Microsoft Office计算器，因为数学和你还有
You've got Liebreich office which is like Microsoft Office calculator because math and you've also got
文本编辑器和大量非常棒的东西都在这里。
text editors and loads of loads of really awesome things on here.
好的，我们将大量使用的一件事当然是航站楼，这就是
OK so one thing that we're going to be making a lot of use of of course is the terminal which is what
你们是来这里学习的。
you guys came here to learn.
所有这些都准备好了，一旦你对此感到满意，它应该会把你带到
So with that all set up and once you've got yourself comfortable with this it should take you about
五分钟左右的时间真的很容易习惯。
five minutes or so it's really easy to get used to.
我们在下一个视频中要做的是让您开始学习如何使用命令
What are we going to do in the next video is get you started learning how to use commands and when it
这里说已经发布了更新的软件，您想现在安装吗？
says here updated software has been issued Do you want to install it now.
当然可以，只需继续并单击立即安装，然后等待安装过程完成
Sure go ahead just go ahead and click Install now and wait for that installation process to complete
它应该自己解决问题。
it should sort itself out on its own.
要求您提供密码。
Ask you for your password.
您必须输入该权限才能继续进行安装，并且您应该
You had to enter that to give it some permission to go ahead and do the installation and you should
有一个完全更新的、随时可以开始学习Linux的系统。
have a fully updated and ready to go system for learning linux on.
当你准备好了，每次你想要启动它的时候，你所要做的就是直接进入
And when you are ready all you've got to do every time you want to launch this is just head over into
虚拟框，然后只需单击“开始”，它就会启动。
virtual box and then just click start and it will boot up.
这是这台现代电脑。
This this this modern computer.
所以你已经完全准备好了，可以出发了。
So there you are you are completely ready to go.
所以我期待着在课程的下一节见到你。
So I look forward to seeing you in the next section of the course.
我们将从学习如何使用终端通信的方式开始，向您展示渐进式设置，我将
We're going to start you off by learning how to use the terminal comm way to show you gradual set I'll
下一个视频再见。
see you in the next video.